<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- Help screen -->

    <!-- Get Started -->
    <string name="text_tv_get_started_section">Get Started</string>
    <string name="text_tv_get_started_subtitle_one">1. Welcome to LOBSTR Vault</string>
    <string name="text_tv_get_started_one_description">"Developed by the creators of LOBSTR - Simple &amp; Secure Stellar Wallet, LOBSTR Vault is the transaction signer app for your mobile device with the local key storage.

LOBSTR Vault uses multisignature technology of the Stellar Network and allows you to create a local signer account and verify transactions from multiple accounts on the Stellar Network.

Your secret key is fully encrypted, securely stored in the local storage and never touches our servers.

The app uses the secret key to sign transactions on-device - you make the final decision to \'Confirm\' or \'Deny\' the transaction.

Quick and easy to use, LOBSTR Vault is an open source app that fully integrates with LOBSTR wallet and takes the security of your Stellar account to the next level.

LOBSTR Vault can be used to secure other wallets and exchanges operating on the Stellar Network, including StellarTerm.com and Stellarport.io.

If you are using LOBSTR wallet, you can find the \'Multisig\' option under the \'Settings\' tab.

With LOBSTR wallet, StellarTerm and Stellarport integration, there is no need to import Transaction XDRs. Your pending outgoing transactions will appear in the signing LOBSTR Vault account automatically in a matter of seconds.

LOBSTR Vault supports push notifications to help you to stay up-to-date with your transaction \'sign\' requests.

A custom 6-digit PIN and your biometric authentication help keeping your signer account safe."
    </string>

    <string name="text_tv_get_started_subtitle_two">2. Intro to multisignature concept</string>
    <string name="text_tv_get_started_two_description">"Stellar Network uses signatures as authorization. Transactions always need authorization from at least one public key in order to be considered valid.

Typically transactions only involve operations on a single account. For example, if account A wants to send lumens to account B, only account A needs to authorize the transaction.

Transaction signatures are created by cryptographically signing the transaction object contents with a secret key.

A transaction with an attached signature is considered to have authorization from that public key or Stellar account.

In two cases, a transaction may need more than one signature:

- If the transaction has operations that affect more than one account, it will need authorization from every account in question.
- A transaction will also need additional signatures if the account associated with the transaction has multiple singers. That is where the multisignature comes in.


Multisignature (or \"multisig\") concept presumes that account requires two or more secret key signatures before allowing a transaction to occur on the account.

For example, two people want to have a joint account so that any transactions made from that account first requires both parties to agree and sign them before it can be submitted.

This increases the security of account, as long as the two or more secret keys are stored separately.


Transactions on the Stellar Network can include one or more operations.

Each operation falls under a specific threshold category: low, medium, or high. Each threshold defines the combined amount of signature weight an operation needs in order to succeed.

Each account can set its own threshold values. By default, all thresholds levels are set to 0, and the master key is set to weight 1.

For the sake of simplicity of use and additional security, at the time of multisig setup, LOBSTR currently sets identical values for all threshold categories and increases them evenly with the addition of new signers.

Be careful and use caution when changing your accounts thresholds in other services as this may lead to a permanent block of your account and a loss of your funds!


For all Stellar wallets, the private key that corresponds to its public key is called the master key.

Each master key can be assigned a weight also referred to as the signature weight of that account.

Each signer account also has its own signature weight.

If you are using LOBSTR Vault paired with LOBSTR wallet or StellarTerm, signature weights of signer keys are the same as the weight of the master key of the primary account.

For the multisig-enabled account, all operations like payments, adding trustlines, updating weights and others will require two or more signatures - one from your account and one or more additional signatures from your signers.

That is where you will need LOBSTR Vault app."
    </string>

    <string name="text_tv_get_started_subtitle_three">3. LOBSTR Vault multisig setup details</string>
    <string name="text_tv_get_started_three_description">"When enabling a multisig for a wallet, you can define how many signatures there should be in total, and how many of them should be required for a transaction to occur on the Stellar Network.

The multisig wallet can be of the M-of-N type where any M private keys out of a possible N are required for a transaction to occur.

For example, a 2-of-3 multisig setup will require a signature from you and another signature from one of your two signers to send funds to another Stellar account.

For the sake of simplicity of use and additional security, LOBSTR only currently supports N-of-N multisig type where a signature of each signer will be required for a transaction to occur.

The support for M-of-N multisig setup will be introduced at a later date.


LOBSTR and StellarTerm currently use the following values when setting up 2-of-2 multisig for your wallet:

- Low, medium and high operation thresholds are set to 20.
- The weight of the master signing key is set to 10.
- The weight of the LOBSTR Vault singer key is set to 10.
- The weight of the LOBSTR Vault marker key is set to 1.

If you add another LOBSTR Vault signer to your wallet (3-of-3 multisig), all operation thresholds will be set to 30 and the new signer will be added with the signing key weight set to 10.


LOBSTR Vault marker key is a static signer key that ends with LOBSTRVAULT.

This key allows third-party services to determine that the account is protected by LOBSTR Vault and that our service should be notified in case of transaction signature requests.

This key does not have enough signer weight to authorize any transaction and is not involved in the process of signing transactions."
    </string>

    <string name="text_tv_get_started_subtitle_four">4. Do I need multisig for my wallet?</string>
    <string name="text_tv_get_started_four_description">"If you are not sure if you should use LOBSTR Vault app and enable multisig for your Stellar account, this guide may help with your decision.


Depending on your cases of day-to-day usage, you may want to enable multisig for your main Stellar account in the following scenarios:

- Additional security and hack prevention

If you are concerned that your private key may be compromised or stolen, enabling multisig will prevent the problems caused by the loss or theft of a private key.

Your funds will be safe even if one of the keys is compromised.

All transactions will require two or more signatures - hackers will not be able to authorize transactions unless they have access to both your main and signer accounts.

- Storing significant funds

As for other your valuables, if you are storing a significant amount of Stellar lumens or other assets in your Stellar account, you may want to double up on the security of your account by enabling multisig.

- Joint account

Multisig can be used if you want to share a Stellar account with another person.

You can set up a multisig solution on that account where you both will need to sign a transaction for it to occur on the Stellar Network.

Anyone will be able to deposit funds into the account, but making transactions will require signatures from the main account and both signing parties.

- Business decisions

You may use a multisig solution to control access to a company\'s funds stored in the Stellar wallet.

For example, you may set up a solution where each board member holds the signing key and a transaction may only occur if all or part of board members agree on the decision.

Using a multisig solution, you can make sure that the funds are not misused.


However, there are certain cases when using multisig may not be ideal for you:

- You can lock yourself out of your Stellar wallet

Using multisig technology can be dangerous if you are not careful and do not store your multiple copies of Recovery Phrase in the secure locations.

A loss of your Recovery Phrase will also result in you losing control of your main account, as you will not be able to sign outgoing transactions due to the lack of required signatures.

- Storing an insignificant amount of funds

If you have an insignificant amount of funds stored in your account, you may want to avoid enabling multisig for your account at first for the sake of simplicity of use.

Not all services fully support multisig accounts as of right now and multisig concept may be challenging for beginners.

If required, you can enable multisig for your account in LOBSTR wallet or StellarTerm at a later date.

- High account activity

If you engage in active asset trading on the Stellar Network or perform a lot of transactions daily, it may not be very practical to have multisig enabled on your account.

In this case, you may want to create a separate multisig account to store the majority of your funds."
    </string>
    <string name="text_tv_get_started_subtitle_five">5. What is a Recovery Phrase?</string>
    <string name="text_tv_get_started_five_description">"A Recovery Phrase, 12 Words Backup or Seed Phrase represent the same thing and have many more names in the cryptocurrency ecosystem which may be misleading.

LOBSTR Vault uses the term \'Recovery Phrase\'.

Recovery Phrase is a list of 12 or 24 words that represent the single secret piece of data that is used to generate both the public and private key of your account.

You are the only one who has access to your Recovery Phrase.

You will need these words to restore access to your LOBSTR Vault account in case your phone is lost or stolen.

Your 12 or 24-word Recovery Phrase is stored in an encrypted manner on the device you install LOBSTR Vault on.

We do not store your Recovery Phrase on our servers, nor do we have any access to it.


The order of the words in the Recovery Phrase is very important!

Make sure to write down the Recovery Phrase in the correct order without any spelling mistakes:

- Start from the word in the top left corner and follow the line to the last word
- Transition down to the next line and start with the first word on the left
- Continue until every word is written down

Write down these 12 words on a piece of paper or print them using a secure printer.

A smart move is to create multiple copies of your Recovery Phase and store it in multiple locations to prevent an inadvertent loss.


You will not be able to access your account without your Recovery Phase. Entering the phrase incorrectly will result in you not being able to access your account as well.

A loss of your Recovery Phrase will also result in losing control of your main account, as you will not be able to sign outgoing transactions due to the lack of required signatures.

Anybody else who discovers the phrase can access your signer account, so it must be kept safe like your other valuables. It must not be stored in any electronic or digital form.

Do not email or screenshot the Recovery Phrase."
    </string>

    <string name="text_tv_get_started_subtitle_six">6. Where can I find my public key?</string>
    <string name="text_tv_get_started_six_description">"Every Stellar account has a public key and a secret key.

The public key is always safe to share — other people need it to identify your account and verify that you authorized a transaction.

You will also need your Vault public key to set up the multisig solution in LOBSTR wallet, StellarTerm or other services.

If you are currently setting up or recovering your LOBSTR Vault account, you can find your public key at the \'Your Vault Public Key\' screen.

Use the \'Copy Key\' button to transfer your key. The QR-code contains your Vault public key as well - you can scan it using your LOBSTR wallet app on another device.

If you are already inside your LOBSTR Vault account, you can find your Vault public key at the \'Home\' screen or in the \'Account\' section of the \'Settings\' screen.


If you try finding your account using a network explorer like StellarExpert, you may receive a message that your account does not exist on Stellar ledger.

Do not worry, your account is safe. It is stored locally in LOBSTR Vault app. The account does not need to actually exist on the Stellar Network to act as a signer for your main account.

If you want to use your LOBSTR Vault account as a wallet, you would need to create and fund this account at first."
    </string>

    <string name="text_tv_how_to_subtitle_seven">7. Where is my private key?</string>
    <string name="text_tv_how_to_seven_description">"The Recovery Phrase is the single secret piece of data that is used to generate both the public and private key for your account.

LOBSTR Vault uses the Recovery Phrase instead of the private key for your convenience.

Your private key is still stored locally and used to encrypt data and sign transactions.

LOBSTR Vault is not a wallet app and does not expose the private key for security reasons.

If you need the private key of your LOBSTR Vault account, you would need to derive it from your 12-word Recovery Phrase using third party tools."
    </string>

    <string name="text_tv_how_to_subtitle_eight">8. What is a Transaction XDR?</string>
    <string name="text_tv_how_to_eight_description">"XDR, also known as External Data Representation, is a binary serialization data format used extensively in the Stellar Network.

The ledger, transactions, results, history, and other data on the Stellar Network are encoded using XDR.

Transactions are the basic unit of change in the Stellar Network and are essentially a grouping of operations. Transaсtions can include one or more operations.

If you have a multisig solution configured on your account, your service or wallet may provide you with Transaction Envelope XDR string.

Transaction Envelope XDR contains the transaction information together with the signature generated using the secret key of your account. If you are using multisig, you will need to add one or more additional signatures for this transaction to be accepted by the network.

This string should be provided to the owner of signing account and imported to the signing service, like LOBSTR Vault or StellarGuard.

The good news is that LOBSTR Vault saves you time and manages this process automatically - you won\'t need to import the Transaction XDR manually.

If you are using LOBSTR Vault paired with LOBSTR wallet, StellarTerm or Stellarport, your pending outgoing transaction will appear in the connected LOBSTR Vault account in a matter of seconds.

Connected LOBSTR Vault account will show a push notification asking to confirm or deny every new transaction.
"
    </string>


    <!-- How To -->
    <string name="text_tv_how_to_section">How To</string>

    <string name="text_tv_how_to_subtitle_nine">9. Recover my LOBSTR Vault account</string>
    <string name="text_tv_how_to_nine_description">"In order to recover your LOBSTR Vault account, you should have your Recovery Phrase you\'ve written down when you created your account.

Our company does not have access to your Recovery Phrase.

It is securely stored in the local storage of your phone until you log out from your LOBSTR Vault account or remove the app.

If you ever lose your phone, remove LOBSTR Vault app accidentally or can\'t access your account for any reason, you can restore the account using the 12-word Recovery Phrase.


Follow the steps below to recover your LOBSTR Vault account:

1. Install LOBSTR Vault app on your iOS or Android device and open it.
2. Choose the Recover Account option.
3. Enter the 12-word Recovery Phrase you\'ve written down when you created your account.
- The word order is very important. Enter the Recovery Phrase in the correct order without any spelling mistakes.
4. If the Recovery Phrase is entered correctly, the \'Next\' button should become active.
5. Set up your custom 6-digit PIN.
6. Enable biometric authentication, if required.

If your account is a signer for another Stellar Account and you followed the steps correctly, the recovery process should now be complete.


You can use the Recover Account option to access the account (signer) created in another signer service, for example, StellarGuard.

Such service should provide the BIP-039 generated 12 or 24-word Recovery Phrase.
You should configure the multisig solution at the LOBSTR side for the system to function properly.

If for some reason, you can\'t install LOBSTR Vault, you can still recover access to your main account. In that case, you would need to derive the signer secret key from your 12-word Recovery Phrase using third party tools.

Once you have a secret key of your LOBSTR Vault signer, you can use it to disable multisig in your main account manually, using a tool like Stellar Laboratory."
    </string>

    <string name="text_tv_how_to_subtitle_ten">10. Add a signer in LOBSTR app</string>
    <string name="text_tv_how_to_ten_description">"This section will guide you through the multisig setup process where you are using a single device with both LOBSTR wallet and LOBSTR Vault apps installed.

Before you start:

- Install LOBSTR wallet app on your device and login into your account
- Make sure you have a Stellar account linked to your LOBSTR account in the app
- Make sure your Stellar account activation credit provided by LOBSTR is paid off
- Your Stellar account should have a sufficient balance to enable a multisig solution - each additional signer increases the base reserve by 0.5 XLM
- Install LOBSTR Vault app on your device


To enable the multisig solution for your Stellar account in LOBSTR wallet using a new signer account from LOBSTR Vault app, follow the steps below:

1. In LOBSTR Vault, select \'Create Account\' option.
2. Carefully read the description and tap the \'I Understand\' button.
3. At the \'Recovery Phrase\' screen, write down the presented Recovery Phrase and tap \'Next\' button.
4. Verify your Recovery Phrase by tapping the words in the correct order and tap \'Next\' button.
5. Create your custom 6 digit PIN.
6. Confirm your custom 6 digit PIN.
7. If enabled on your device, protect your account by enabling biometric authentication.
8. You will be transitioned to the screen with the Vault public key and the QR code.
9. In LOBSTR wallet app, open the \'Settings\' screen and select the \'Multisig\' option.
10. Tap \'Enable Multisig\' button.
11. LOBSTR wallet should detect LOBSTR Vault account automatically and prompt to use it.
12. Tap \'Yes, Use This Device\' button.
13. At this step, you will need to confirm that you want to add a new signer to your Stellar account. Carefully read the description and tap the \'Continue\' button.
14. If the \'Multisig enabled\' screen is displayed, the singer account should be successfully added to your Stellar account.
15. To complete the setup at LOBSTR Vault side, open the app and tap the \'Next\' button at the screen with your Vault public key.
16. If required, tap the \'Re-Check\' button at the next screen.
17. You will be transitioned to the '\Home\' screen of LOBSTR Vault app.

If you followed the steps correctly, your LOBSTR Stellar account should be protected by LOBSTR Vault signer account."
    </string>

    <string name="text_tv_signing_subtitle_eleven">11. Add a Transaction XDR manually</string>
    <string name="text_tv_signing_eleven_description">"If you have multisig enabled for your Stellar account and try to make a transaction, you may be provided with a Transaction XDR by your wallet or signer service.

It is likely that you need additional signatures for this transaction to occur on your account.

If you are using LOBSTR Vault paired with LOBSTR wallet, StellarTerm or Stellarport, transaction \'sign\' requests should appear automatically in LOBSTR Vault in most cases - there is no need to import Transaction XDRs.

LOBSTR Vault parses the XDR and shows you the operations in a human-readable format.
Always verify the contents of transaction before adding a signature.


If you are using other service and need to add and sign a Transaction XDR in LOBSTR Vault app, follow the steps below:

1. Select the \'Transactions\' screen in the main navigation.
2. Tap the \'+\' floating button.
3. Paste your Transaction XDR into the input field of \'Add Transaction XDR\' form.
4. Tap the \'Next\' button.
5. Review the details of the transaction and tap the \'Confirm\' button.

If the \'Success\' screen is displayed - your transaction should be successfully signed.

You may be provided with another Transaction XDR if you need more signatures on this transaction.


If the \'Add Transaction XDR\' form displays errors or the \'Submit\' button is disabled:

- Make sure you\'ve copied the Transaction XDR correctly - there should be no spaces before and after the XDR string.
- Make sure you are using the correct XDR - a transaction is considered invalid if it includes signatures that aren\'t needed to authorize the transaction."
    </string>

    <string name="text_tv_signing_subtitle_twelve">12. Change or reset my PIN</string>
    <string name="text_tv_signing_twelve_description">"In order to change the PIN of your LOBSTR Vault account, perform the following steps:

1. Select the \'Settings\' screen in the main navigation
2. Select the \'Change PIN\' option in the \'Security\' section
3. Enter your current PIN
4. Enter your new desired PIN
5. Confirm your new desired PIN


If you can\'t remember your PIN or your biometric authentication does not match, you will need to go through the recovery process in order to access your account.

There is no ability to request a PIN reset in LOBSTR Vault app.

Before you log out from your LOBSTR Vault account, make sure you have secured your Recovery Phrase. You will not be able to recover your account or sign in without your Recovery Phrase - your account will be lost.

Refer to the \'How To\' section for instructions on the account recovery process.
"
    </string>

    <!-- Signing transactions in LOBSTR Vault app -->
    <string name="text_tv_signing_section">Signing Transactions</string>

    <string name="text_tv_signing_subtitle_thirteen">13. Which transactions can I sign?</string>
    <string name="text_tv_signing_thirteen_description">"Transactions in the Stellar Network are made up of a list of operations but mostly include only one operation.

LOBSTR Vault allows signing transactions with one or many operations.

You can view the details of each transaction and the operations to be executed at the \'Transaction Details\' screen.


List of Stellar Network Operation Types:

1. Create Account
Creates a new account in Stellar network.

2. Payment
Sends a simple payment between two accounts in Stellar network.

3. Path Payment
Sends a path payment between two accounts in the Stellar network.

4. Manage Offer
Creates, updates or deletes an offer in the Stellar network.

5. Create Passive Offer
Creates an offer that won\'t consume a counter offer that exactly matches this offer.

6. Set Options
Sets account options (inflation destination, adding signers, etc.)

7. Change Trust
Creates, updates or deletes a trust line.

8. Allow Trust
Updates the \"authorized\" flag of an existing trust line this is called by the issuer of the related asset.

9. Account Merge
Deletes account and transfers remaining balance to the destination account.

10. Inflation
Runs inflation.

11. Manage Data
Set, modify or delete a Data Entry (name/value pair) for an account.

12. Bump Sequence
Bumps forward the sequence number of an account."
    </string>

    <string name="text_tv_signing_subtitle_fourteen">14. Transaction requires more signatures</string>
    <string name="text_tv_signing_fourteen_description">"If the main Stellar account has multiple signers, you may see a message that more signatures are needed for the transaction to occur at the \'Success\' screen.

In most cases, this means that other signers for the main account should provide their signatures by \'Confirming\' the transaction.

Such transaction will not occur on the Stellar Network until it is signed by all signers including the main account.

If you are using LOBSTR Vault paired with LOBSTR wallet, StellarTerm or Stellarport, all signers will be notified of the transaction \'sign\' requests automatically.


In case you need more signatures, the \'Success\' screen will also display a Transaction XDR.

You may treat this string as the desired transaction signed using the secret key of your LOBSTR Vault account.

You can copy a Transaction XDR and provide it to other signers if there are issues with transaction not appearing in LOBSTR Vault automatically."
    </string>


    <string name="text_tv_signing_subtitle_fifteen">15. Invalid sequence number</string>
    <string name="text_tv_signing_fifteen_description">"Each transaction on the Stellar Network has a sequence number. Transactions follow a strict ordering rule when it comes to processing of transactions for each account.

For a transaction to be valid, the sequence number must be strictly 1 greater than the sequence number stored in the source account entry when the transaction is applied.

For example, if you are using LOBSTR Vault and LOBSTR wallet, the source account is the Stellar account used in LOBSTR wallet.


For accounts with multisig setup, there is a probability of multiple unsigned transactions existing with the same sequence number, waiting to be signed and submitted to the Stellar Network.

Such transactions do not exist on the Stellar Network until all signatures are provided.

Only one of those transactions can ultimately occur on the Stellar Network with the given sequence number.

Once one of those transactions is accepted and applied to the ledger, other transactions will be rendered invalid and will not be accepted by the Stellar Network.

An attempt to sign a transaction with an outdated sequence number in LOBSTR Vault will fail with the \'Sequence number does not match source account\' message.

Such transactions will be marked as \'Invalid\' at the \'Transactions\' screen of the LOBSTR Vault app.

You will need to remove such transactions from your transaction list manually by choosing the \'Deny\' option at the \'Transaction Details\' screen.


An attempt to sign a transaction will also fail for the same reason if the sequence number is greater than the sequence number stored in the source account entry by 2 or more.

In this case, a transaction will be considered valid once the sequence number stored in the source account entry reaches the required value."
    </string>

    <string name="text_tv_signing_subtitle_sixteen">16. Prompt for transaction decisions</string>
    <string name="text_tv_signing_sixteen_description">"The \'Prompt for transaction decisions\' switcher is used to control the appearance of the additional confirmation alert when you are making a decision to confirm or deny a transaction.

As some transactions may potentially be harmful to your account once accidentally signed, LOBSTR Vault by default asks for double confirmation at the time of transaction signing.

If the switcher is disabled, the \'Are you sure?\' alert will not appear when you sign a transaction.

Be careful and use caution if you choose to disable the switcher. LOBSTR recommends leaving the switcher enabled at all times."
    </string>

    <string name="text_tv_signing_subtitle_seventeen">17. I accidentally confirmed a transaction</string>
    <string name="text_tv_signing_seventeen_description">"All transactions on the Stellar Network are stored in a decentralized ledger and are final, non-reversible and non-editable.

If you successfully \'Confirmed\' a transaction in LOBSTR Vault and no additional signatures are required, the transaction is final and can not be reversed.

LOBSTR is not able to refund/revert a transaction, so please ensure that all the details are correct before signing.

If you successfully \'Confirmed\' a transaction in LOBSTR Vault and additional signatures are required, it will be up to other transaction signers to \'Confirm\' or \'Deny\' the transaction.

The transaction will not be published on the Stellar Network until it contains the required signatures from all signers.

If you successfully \'Denied\' a transaction in LOBSTR Vault, the transaction is rendered no longer valid and you will need to create a new transaction.
"
    </string>

    <!-- Signing transactions in LOBSTR Vault app -->
    <string name="text_tv_other_section">Other</string>

    <string name="text_tv_signing_subtitle_eighteen">18. Supported wallets and services</string>
    <string name="text_tv_signing_eighteen_description">"At the moment LOBSTR Vault signer app fully integrates and operates with LOBSTR wallet, StellarTerm open source client and Stellarport wallet.

LOBSTR wallet also supports StellarGuard multisig provider.

LOBSTR Vault can be easily integrated with other service operating on Stellar to bring advanced multisignature capabilities and increase the security of your account.

We are working on increasing support for LOBSTR Vault across many applications."
    </string>

    <string name="text_tv_signing_subtitle_nineteen">19. Integrate LOBSTR Vault support</string>
    <string name="text_tv_signing_nineteen_description">Are you a representative or a developer of a wallet, exchange or service on the Stellar Network and looking to integrate the support of the LOBSTR Vault signer app with your solution?

\n\nWe would be happy to assist you with a simple integration. Please visit the following page for details: <a href="https://lobstr.co/vault/">https://lobstr.co/vault/</a>.
    </string>

    <string name="text_tv_signing_subtitle_twenty">20. Still have issues?</string>
    <string name="text_tv_signing_twenty_description">If your question is not listed in the Help section or you are having issues with the LOBSTR Vault app, reach out to us using the support email listed below or contact LOBSTR support.

\n\nSupport email: <a href="mailto:support@lobstr.co">support@lobstr.co</a>.
\n
    </string>

</resources>